[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hippopotamuses may seem slow, lazy and bulky but in fact are one of the most dangerous African animals. Which of the following should you avoid in order to prevent a hippopotamus attack?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Standing between the hippopotamus and its calf", "Surprising the hippopotamus", "Blocking the hippopotamus\u2019 way"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Wilson brothers teamed up for this 2001 dramatic comedy with an ensemble cast including Ben Stiller and Anjelica Houston.", "correct_answer": "The Royal Tenenbaums", "incorrect_answers": ["Starsky and Hutch", "Anchorman", "Bottle Rocket"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Peace Symbol, which became an icon of the 1960s anti-war movement, derives from what?", "correct_answer": "two semaphoric signals", "incorrect_answers": ["a slightly twisted cross", "None of these", "an image of a nuclear bomber"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tetris, the popular falling-blocks video game, was invented in Russia.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Ramphotyphlops braminus, a harmless blind snake species, found in Africa and Asia, is often mistaken for this animal.", "correct_answer": "Earthworm", "incorrect_answers": ["Black mamba", "Dog-faced water snake", "Elephant Trunk Snake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the popular name of the artificial island in Tokyo Bay, whose name is Yume No Shima in Japanese?", "correct_answer": "Dream Island", "incorrect_answers": ["Water Lilly", "Wind Island", "Sun Island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This mammal is known for its black fur with a white stripe and for its apparent odor.", "correct_answer": "Skunk", "incorrect_answers": ["Sloth", "Ferret", "Weasel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Autophobia means fear of cars.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of the national anthem of Spain?", "correct_answer": "The Royal March", "incorrect_answers": ["My Precious Kingdom", "God Save Spain", "Proud Spain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie star delivered the following line: Let off some steam Bennett?", "correct_answer": "Arnold Schwarzenegger in Commando", "incorrect_answers": ["Chuck Norris in Missing in Action II", "Harrison Ford in Air Force One", "Sylvester Stallone in Cobra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Taste is related to what other basic sense?", "correct_answer": "Smell", "incorrect_answers": ["Balance", "Vision", "Hearing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the first spacecraft to study Mars?", "correct_answer": "Mariner 4", "incorrect_answers": ["Viking 1", "Mars 2", "Viking 2"]}]